Aaron Hannah Shakespeare

As a seasoned international model, I've thrived in environments that demand adaptability, resilience and patience. Engaging with a wide variety of clients in the fashion industry I was able to adapt to new workflows, teams, environments and spoken languages on many creative projects. This career gave me the opportunity to travel the world, immersing myself in experiences that have shaped me into a flexible and determined person.

I have recently completed the 12-week bootcamp with Just IT in Software Development (Software Skills).

Throughout this period I find myself becoming even more enthusiastic about programming, no doubt passion for technology will continue to inspire my continuous learning and ultimately, career progression in the industry.

My passion for technology began with my first home computer, the iMac G3, which sparked a curiosity that has endured over the years. The hardware and operating system of this computer were unlike anything I had encountered before, prompting me to delve into MacOS and grapple with understanding different operating systems and compatibility nuances.

Engaging in creative arts activities is a vital hobby for me, whether I'm participating or spectating. I find the arts enriching to my personal journey and see it as a valuable outlet for my self-expression. As a member of multiple marginalized communities, I understand and embrace the importance of approaching challenges from diverse perspectives. Additionally, my interests stretch through the arts, technology and community. From fixing up an old PC, attending exhibitions, live music, and gaming.

In my last role, I took on many responsibilities in a field of personal interest, a tattoo studio. As a personal, administration and social media assistant I gained skills regarding customer care etiquette and being incredibly detailed with maintaining the studio space.

AARON HANNAH SHAKESPEARE

Aaron Hannah Shakespeare

PROFILE

Transitioning from the fast-paced world of fashion to the dynamic realm of technology has been a natural progression in fulfilling my interests.

As I commit to continuous learning as a programmer, I find motivation through the satisfaction of understanding new tools, concepts and problem solving.

EXPERIENCE

Self Employed, Worldwide — Fashion Model

March 2017 - PRESENT

- Liaising with agencies and clients in various countries.
- Learning basics of new languages to help bridge language barriers.
- Planning travel and accommodation.
- Working on projects with large new teams, understanding client needs and project objectives.
- Sustaining mental and physical performance for extended hours.
- Upholding embargo and NDA.

Femme Fatale Tattoo, London — Personal/General/Studio Assistant

June 2022 - October 2022

- Coordinating with external partners to facilitate stock delivery and maintain optimal inventory levels.
- Creating social media content and responding to enquiries.
- Validating age and consent forms.

EDUCATION

Just IT, London — Software Skills

April 2024 - June 2024

A three month bootcamp, during which I was able to learn new language skills and refine concepts learnt from self-study.

New City College (Epping Forest College), Essex — BTEC 2012

Performing Arts & Dance | Distinction - Distinction - Distinction

Roding Valley High School, Essex — *GCSE* 2008

English – B | Maths – C | Science – C | Total - 12